WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
www.tvsubtitles.net
Poor Brian.
It was a bomb.
Someone...planted a bomb.
Ted tell you?
How many people?
Four dead.
67 wounded.
11 of them critical.
It's a hell of a thing.
Not something I ever expected
to happen in Pittsburgh.
What about Michael?
I...
I spoke to Debbie a couple of
minutes ago. He's still in surgery.
Any idea who did it?
No.
Obviously...someone
who didn't care for Stop Prop 14.
I'd prefer if you
didn't touch anything.
We're interviewing everyone
who worked here.
I'm going to need statements
from you two as well.
And a...copy of the guest list.
Not a problem.
Why don't you two...go home?
Come on. Let's stop by the hospital,
see if there's an update.
Uh...you go.
I've got too much to do here.
I've got to...
..get that list to the cops.
Got to...call the insurance company.
Get some estimates for how
much it's going to cost to rebuild.
Ted. It's 7am.
Em, honey,
would you sit down, already?
Sorry.
Why in the fuck doesn't somebody
tell us something?
I'm sure they will
once there's something to tell.
Can I get you anything
from the cafeteria?
Coffee? A muffin?
No, thanks, sunshine.
Do you think something's wrong?
They haven't said anything.
Don't go there, please.
Please, don't.
Any word?
Uh-uh.
We're still waiting.
Yeah. I'm no good at that.
Some of us have. Others,
not so much.
Did you talk to Carl?
Did he say anything?
Uh...he said that he loves you
and that he wishes he was here.
And...that it was a bomb.
Oh, my God.
What the hell did you think it was?
What kind of sick fuck
would do something like that?!
The kind that went
to Matthew Shepherd's funeral
with signs saying
'Your Son's Burning in Hell'.
The kind we saw driving down
Liberty Avenue with bullhorns
shouting their hate slogans.
The kind that support
Proposition 14.
Tommy, leave it alone.
I have to go.
Honey?
I...I'll be at home. Call me
as soon as you hear anything.
The whole world's gone crazy.
Whole fucking world's just...
Oh.
Dr Ryan?
We had to remove his spleen.
There was also a lot of internal
bleeding, as we suspected.
But we managed to stop it.
Will he be alright?
I'm cautiously optimistic.
I think he'll be fine.
Thank you, God.
I told him
he'd better look after Michael
if he knew what was good for him.
Can we see Michael?
He's in Recovery now.
He'll be sleeping
for most of the day,
so why don't you all go home
and get some rest?
I...
Why don't we all go home
and get some rest?
I'm going to st...stick around
for a while.
Why don't you go, honey, huh?
Take a shower.
Don't you have a class?
Oh, God, no, I couldn't.
What if he wakes up?
The doctor said
he'll be sleeping most of the day.
There's no point
in the two of us sitting here.
You'd better listen to what she says.
God did.
That's wonderful!
You must be so relieved.
We're all relieved.
We'll be by later.
Do you need anything?
Well, be sure to take care
of yourself. That's important too.
'Bye.
Michael's going to be alright!
They expect a full recovery.
Thank God.
Ooh. Oops.
What are you doing?
I don't want to put a curse on it.
Did you hear that, sweetie?
Daddy's going to be as good as new.
Yep.
I realised something
when I woke up this morning.
Oh, yeah? What's that?
That I want to see your face
first thing
every day for the rest of my life.
Yours too.
Mommy, I want my breakfast.
Oh, sorry.
The master wants his banana.
We should go to the hospital.
Why don't we stop by this afternoon?
Maybe Dusty can watch the kids.
Mommy.
It's coming.
Hey, Marie, it's Mel.
Is Dusty there?
What's wrong?
Oh, God.
What? What is it?
Uh, we didn't know. I, uh...
We didn't hear anything, so we just
assumed that everything was ok. I...
We'll...we'll be over
as soon as we can.
ok.
What?
Dusty, she, uh...
..she was one of the...
Oh, God.
Oh!
Thank God my mother
has congestive heart failure.
If I didn't have to be with her,
I would've been there last night.
Oh.
Is everyone present
and accounted for?
Except for Phil
from the art department.
He got trampled on when everyone
was trying to get out.
Broken hip.
He'll be laid up for a month.
I'll give him a call.
And send some food...and porn.
The basic essentials.
Jesus, Brian...
what are you doing here?
You should be at home
getting some shut-eye.
I tried.
Well, you'll be happy to know
that I already submitted a claim
to the insurance company.
I've spoken with three contractors.
They're submitting bids.
And the building inspector's
checking
to make sure
the structure's sound, so...
Aren't you forgetting something?
Are you going to ask how Michael is?
Right. I was just about to.
He made it through surgery.
He's going to be alright.
Well, that's, uh...
that's great news.
So...why don't you put the estimates
and contractors and the inspectors
on hold for a minute,
haul your ass down to the hospital?
I'm afraid you'll have to bring
bouquets and bonbons without me,
since, at the moment,
I'm trying to get your business
back up and running
as quickly as possible.
For which, by the way,
I don't expect a thankyou.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I put a call in to Dusseldorf
Plumbing about a broken water main.
Klaus, hi. Sorry to keep you
on hold so long.
Does anybody know who did it?
It was some fucking lunatic.
Or Jerry Falwell.
Isn't that what I just said?
I, uh, assume you're all aware
of what happened last night?
Yeah, the entire world's
aware of it - it was on cnn.
Right, in that case,
I think we should forgo
discussing the homosexual subtext
in the works of Willa Cather,
and focus instead on how we respond
to hate crimes and acts of violence.
I'll tell you how - we do exactly
to them what they did to us.
What good does eye for an eye do?
There'll just be more blind fools
running around.
We're fighting for our lives.
Every time some priest or politician
starts spouting off
about how homosexuality's immoral
or a sin,
they give some free permission
to attack us?
You really want to stoop
to their level?
Those drag queens at Stonewall
weren't stooping
when they stood up to the cops.
I don't disagree
freedom has to be fought for,
but I believe our weapons
should be reason, compassion.
The kind of compassion
they showed us last night?
It's true. You can afford the
enlightened way, Professor Bruckner.
You teach at university,
make a good salary.
You can even pass for straight
if you wanted to.
You live in a bubble.
Nothing can touch you.
He's right.
Mm-hm.
My partner...
..my husband was critically injured
last night in the bombing.
He nearly died.
If I live in a bubble...
..it just burst.
Hey, you!
Come on, if you want a ride.
Hey. Come jogging with me.
Five miles.
ok. Make it two.
It'll do you good. Exercise
always makes me feel better.
I am exercising. See?
When I was a boy
and the world was dark and gloomy -
which was pretty much every day -
Aunt Lula would make me
vanilla pudding with maple syrup.
How I kept my figure,
I'll never know,
but...always cheered me up.
They asked me to say a few words
tonight, at the candlelight vigil.
Yes. Turned them down?
I said yes.
Why so surprised?
Well...what you said
about being a professional fag.
This is nothing to do
with being gay or straight.
It's about being a human being.
Men.
That's us!
I'm glad Debbie's son's
going to be ok.
It's a relief for all of us.
It's been a rough night.
There's plenty of pudding.
I'll pass.
I'm going to shower
and grab a quick nap
and head over to the hospital.
What's your name?
You can call me Vera, if you like.
You live in Los Angeles?
No.
So, how about coming with me?
To the vigil?
Actually, I don't think so.
Then we'll meet up?
Actually, I'm not going.
Actually, you should.
It's to honour all those
who were killed or injured.
I know what it's for.
I'd prefer to stay here.
Eating your pudding?
You go. Tell me all about it.
The deal was that we take turns.
You know, first you, then me.
Well, you've had your turn,
so go home and get some sleep.
Right, I'm going.
Good.
In a few minutes.
Alright, then.
At least let me get you some soup.
That'd be nice.
Chicken noodle, if they have it.
Here, let me give you some money.
I can afford to buy you
a cup of soup.
Make it a bowl.
You know, I was...I was, um...
I was just sitting here, thinking
the last time he was in the hospital,
he...he was eight years old.
He had to have his tonsils out.
He was scared shitless.
And, uh, I bought him
one of those little flashlights,
you know, on the end of a key chain?
Oh, yeah.
And we turned it on right before
he was wheeled into surgery.
I told him it'd keep him safe.
And he believed that?
Of course not,
but it took his mind off things.
So, where's my flashlight?
Sweetheart!
Hey! Baby!
You scared the shit out of us.
Mmm. But the doctor said
you're going to be fine.
Oh, that's good.
Wh...what happened?
Some lunatic planted a fucking bomb!
Let's not talk about that now.
You just rest.
Yeah. Yeah, Ben's right.
You've been through a lot.
You just get better.
That's all that matters.
And we're going to be
right here with you.
So, where in the hell's that soup
you were promising me?
Be right back, brown eyes.
Well, don't look so surprised.
I love how you've kept
the original details.
Rusty pipes.
Filthy windows.
The grime-covered walls.
It may not be the country manor of
my dreams with stables and a pool,
but at least it's mine.
You hungry?
What have you got?
I don't.
Then why did you ask?
I can go get something.
Spare yourself the trip.
I just...stopped by
to see if you were alright.
I'm fine, thanks.
Good.
I thought if anyone would come
through all this unruffled,
it'd be you.
When I was bashed, I found out
that the best way to survive -
to go on - is to make something.
A painting, a napkin holder -
it doesn't matter.
Just so that you can prove
to yourself and to them
that they didn't get you,
you're still here.
Well, I'm glad you are.
Brian, you're going to get paint
all over yourself.
Doesn't matter. Didn't you hear
what I said to you last night?
Yes, I heard. You said you love me.
Then how about marrying me?
What?
Stop being ridiculous.
I'm not being ridiculous.
I mean it.
You don't mean it.
How could Mr 'I Believe in Fucking,
Not Love' mean it?
You detest marriage.
You detest anybody who enters into
an imitation heterosexual union
that, by its very nature,
is doomed to fail.
Did I get that right?
Hmm. Word-perfect.
But I've changed my mind.
Well, so have I.
I have no intention
of marrying someone
who, by his very nature,
is doomed to fail.
Besides, you're only asking me
'cause you're freaked out
about what happened to Michael.
I did have this dream.
I was at his funeral, but...
..he wasn't in the coffin, I was.
There. You see?
Now, as soon as life returns
to normal, so will you.
Back from the dead.
Not without you.
I know you too well. Way too well.
Now, thank you for saying it,
but...the answer's no.
Disney World? You went
to fucking Disney World?!
Let him talk, Ma.
Yeah, Deb. Let him talk.
Fine. I'll just feed you
and keep my mouth shut.
When I was a kid,
I'd ask my mom to take me
and she'd always say,
"Sure, honey, next summer."
But we never went.
So I took myself and hitched.
You hitched?!
You'll be happy to know
I didn't blow any of the drivers.
You're a good boy.
I'll, um...
I'll check in on you later.
That's the last we'll see of her.
I'm glad you finally
got to Disney World.
I even got a job there.
Doing what?
I was a dwarf.
You were a dwarf?
Dopey. I was pretty good at it too.
I'm thinking maybe
I'll become an actor.
You can be anything you want -
right after you become a doctor.
Now it's my turn. Huh?
You just lie there
and keep your mouth shut.
Anyway, when I saw the news
about Babylon, I tried calling,
but there was no answer,
so I called Eli and Monty.
They told me what happened.
I got the first plane I could.
You're going to be alright,
aren't you?
Now that you're here.
You still sitting there
eating pudding?
I made a big batch.
..classic, 'Sorry, Wrong Number',
starring Barbara Stanwyck.
You ever see this movie
'Sorry, Wrong Number',
starring Miss Barbara Stanwyck?
Can't says I did.
She keeps getting phone calls
from someone who wants to kill her.
It's her husband.
Thought you never saw it.
If I can't solve a Hollywood movie,
I should retire.
She never leaves her bed
and wears a fabulous peignoir.
Yeah, I can see why
it appeals to you.
Why don't you get dressed
and come see Michael with me?
He's awake.
My God.
But it's not good for him
to have too many visitors.
What? Why are you
looking at me like that?
As someone who's questioned
thousands of suspects,
you're about the worst liar
I've ever heard.
Alright, Miss Marple. I confess.
I can't get off the fucking couch.
The thought of leaving
the house terrifies me.
You're in shock.
I've seen it happen
time and time again.
So, what am I going to do? Live
the rest of my life in seclusion?
Jumping out of my skin
every time I hear a noise?
Case in point.
Hello?
Yeah.
No, I'm leaving right now.
I'll see you in a bit.
Let me tell you
about this kid on the force.
He didn't just want to be a cop.
He had to be Supercop.
His first day on the beat,
he's dealing with this
run-of-the-mill domestic quarrel.
Suddenly,
the husband takes out a gun...
..and shoots his wife
and his little girl,
right before his eyes.
Next day,
Supercop can't get out of bed.
Literally, he couldn't move
his arms or his legs.
I know the feeling.
So he just laid there like that
until this brilliant realisation
came over him.
Bad things happen.
And just because it's supposed to be
your job to prevent them,
sometimes you can't.
All he could do
was live his life each day.
That's all he had. That's all
he had any...control over.
So, did he finally get out of bed?
Yeah. I did.
I got out of bed and I went to work.
And every day since then,
I thank God for one more day
and I pray that I don't waste it.
It looks worse than it is.
Mostly superficial damage.
Structurally, the building's sound.
That's a relief.
So, how much are we looking at
and how long?
I'd say roughly 100 grand
and four to six weeks.
Let me run it past the boss.
I'll get back to you.
Alright.
Would you look at that?
Must be my lucky day.
Well, that's only the beginning.
Contractor just told me that Babylon
will be back on its dancing feet
in no time
with enough insurance money left
to put in that new sound system.
That's good news.
Except I've decided
not to reopen the club.
What?
Babylon. It's history.
But it's your baby, it's your toy,
your personal playground.
Well, now it's a battleground.
So, what are you
going to do with it?
Well, you said there are developers
who want to tear it down,
put up a mini mall.
And you said you'd sooner die than
see our happy homo home homogenised.
Enough people have already died.
Anyway...who'd pay 20 bucks
to dance to the memory
of bombs and corpses?
See you at the vigil.
Huh?
The vigil tonight - see you there.
Oh, yeah, sure.
A meat loaf, a rotisserie chicken,
mixed vegetables, roasted potatoes,
a quart of fruit salad
and a dozen lemon bars.
And that goes to Dusty...
I mean, to Marie Logan.
Here's the address.
I'm usually not the one
to be in denial,
since I'm always expecting
the worst anyway.
But this? I just...
I can't believe Dusty's dead,
Michael was nearly killed.
Not to mention all the others.
I know.
It's just not sinking in.
Give it time.
To be hysterical, fall apart?
I can hardly wait.
Look at that one.
Food's sent.
At least that'll be one less thing
Marie will have to deal with.
You know what she told me?
She has no legal rights
to those kids.
Prop 14 passes, she wouldn't be
allowed to adopt them.
The state could even
take them away from her.
God!
It's a good thing you guys are both
Gus and J.R.'s legal parents.
See how long it is before they try
and take away third-parent adoption.
All I can think about is,
what if it had been one of us?
How would we feel
knowing we'd wasted
the last day we'd ever had together
unreconciled and apart?
The good news is that didn't happen.
We realised what we lost
before it was too late.
Shrink doubled
my dose of Prozac.
Got anything to wash it down with?
Who do I look like to you?
Judy Garland?
Thanks.
Christ, what a nightmare.
You seen Michael?
Uh, yeah. I went to the hospital.
I spoke to Debbie.
She's a fucking inspiration.
I can tell she's had
a profound influence.
I just thank God Justin's alright.
And you.
So...you want to sell your loft?
That's the plan.
You're my fourth call of the day -
people wanting to flee
Liberty Avenue.
Wouldn't have pegged you
as a panic seller.
I'm not.
Have you told Justin?
And I'd prefer if you didn't either.
I respect my clients' privacy.
Anyway, what's the point?
I ask him to marry me...
You what?
Don't worry. He turned me down.
I didn't know.
I just need to do this now.
It can't wait.
Uh...it's your call.
If you could just...sign these.
Um...would you like me
to leave you a couple?
No.
Oh, God.
Thanks.
Uh...for what it's worth,
I just want you to know
that I'm...sorry that I'm not
going to be your mother-in-law.
I was asked to say
a few words tonight.
I asked, "Why?"
They said, "Because you're a hero."
A hero.
Because I play football?
Because after a lifetime of denial,
I was finally honest about who I am?
I don't call that heroic.
What is heroic is standing up
for the rights you deserve,
no matter what the consequences.
And that's exactly what
those who were injured
and who lost their lives last night
were doing.
Or trying to
before they were stopped.
But they were up against
a powerful opponent - hatred.
Hatred spread by those
that want to deny others
what's rightfully theirs...
..in the name of their God...
..their family...
..their country.
I guess they forgot
that America belongs to everyone.
Now let us take a moment of silence
for those who lost their lives.
My son, Michael Novotny...
..was injured in the explosion
last night.
It was touch and go f...for a while.
I'm here to say...
..that he's going to be alright.
But there are others
who are not so lucky.
Your son should have died!
Your son should burn in hell!
What did you say?!
Fags deserve to die!
Fags are an abomination!
Her son will burn in hell!
Fuck you!
Come on, give it to him!
You're the one
who should die, motherfucker!
Hey, get off of him!
Show that faggot who's boss!
Bunch of sick faggots!
Come on, fag boy! Let's roll!
Come on, that's enough.
Get that faggot off him!
That's enough. That's enough!
You don't know
what it is to be human,
much less a Christian!
Fucking...
Get out of here. Get out!
Cops are here.
Cops.
The cops are here, you freak.
Place is kind of empty tonight.
Everyone's at that vigil.
Why aren't you?
Fucking's the best revenge.
Neighbour down the hall from me
was there.
Lost his leg.
One of my best friends got hurt too.
How's he doing?
I don't know.
I haven't been to the hospital.
I thought you said
he was a good friend.
It never would have happened
if it weren't for me.
The explosion?
His getting hurt.
I sent him over to the bar
to get a drink,
and that's where the bomb went off.
Well, what do you know?
It's nice to meet you.
What?
I always wanted to meet God.
And not only did I meet him,
I fucked him.
Will you just go, please?
It's your suite, sweetheart.
But don't you think you're giving
yourself too much credit?
That you're the one responsible?
If I'd gone to get
the goddamn drink myself...
But you didn't, Blanche.
So, what are you going to do?
Nail yourself to the cross?
There. You're absolved.
Oh, God. What did I just do?
Nearly killed someone.
Do you have something to, uh...
Here.
It's my come towel.
For when you're on the go.
I'm not bleeding.
Oh, God, how could I have done that?
If you hadn't, I would have.
I was completely out of control.
I've never been
completely out of control.
You should try it more often.
Who knows? I might like you better.
No, you don't understand.
What I did, it goes against
everything I believe in,
everything I tell my students.
It makes me no different
than those monsters.
Does that mean
I can't call you 'Zen Ben' anymore?
You call me 'Zen Ben'?
Yeah.
No.
Oh, you know,
Gandhi was a Marlboro Man.
You know,
you're a terrible influence.
I try my best.
I don't know what
the Buddha would say -
we haven't talked for a while -
but...
..I do know that your husband
would be damn proud of you.
Well, if anyone knows Michael...
you do.
Did.
He knew you were at that hospital.
That you nearly took
that doctor's head off
because he wouldn't
take your blood...
Listen, Professor.
Mrs Novotny-Bruckner
made it quite clear...
..just because we've been friends
for our whole lives
is no reason to go on being friends.
Thank you.
Thanks.
What the hell's this supposed to be?
I'm not sure.
But I make it a general rule not
to eat anything that's still moving.
How can you fuck up jello?
So, when's Michael going home?
I don't know. The doctor's going to
talk to us later.
Well, what do you think -
two days, a week?
What's your hurry?
You got a plane to catch?
That's $5.50, please.
You do have a plane to...!
What's the matter? Snow White
can't make do with six dwarves?
I can pay for myself.
Sorry. It's grandmother's rights.
It's for both.
$10, thank you.
Thanks.
I didn't hear you.
Thank you.
Better.
So, let me ask you something.
If you knew that were going to just
turn around and take off again...
..why'd the hell you even come back?
I wanted to make sure he was ok.
Yeah?
They've got phones for that, email.
Eugh. God.
Is that what they call meat sauce?
No, there's got to be
some other reason
that you journeyed all the way
from the Magic Kingdom.
I told you.
Then maybe it would have been better
if you hadn't come back at all.
You see, they were just beginning
to accept the fact that you're gone.
Maybe you're right.
I'm not always right.
In fact, sometimes I'm dead wrong.
But I'm thinking
that maybe you came back
because you miss them
as much as they miss you.
And maybe you were even hoping that
if you came back...
..they might ask you to stay.
Let me have a taste
of that mac and cheese.
Jesus.
Where did you learn how to run?
Marilyn Monroe - 'Some Like It Hot'.
You know, her scene.
"Wait for Sugar!"
Couldn't you pretend
to be De Niro
or Schwarzenegger in that movie
where he's running all the time?
Somehow I missed that one.
And there are limits
to the human imagination.
Besides, I don't have to pretend
I'm a movie hero today,
because today I am a real one.
Look at that. Huh?
Is that not a thing of beauty?
Really gave it
to that fucker, didn't I?
Yeah, I'd say
you packed quite a punch.
I won't bore you
with the details -
the time back in Hazelhurst my daddy
tried to teach me how to box -
but...let's just say,
if I'd learned how to defend myself
that bright summer day,
who knows how different
my life might have been?
Well, now you know.
Who'd had ever guessed you could use
a fist for something else?
I told Marie I'd go back
to the house after dinner,
help out.
I'll stay with the kids.
It broke my heart to say Maddie
just standing there at Dusty's grave,
holding that flower.
Only two,
and she's lost one of her mommies.
Next week's Kelly's birthday.
They were planning a party.
You don't really think they could
take those kids away from her,
do you?
I don't know.
Linz...
Oh...never mind.
We'll talk about it later.
No. Tell me.
When the minister said it was time
for us to say goodbye to Dusty...
..I felt like I was saying goodbye
to something else as well.
Like what?
I don't know.
A belief.
An assumption that, with a little
hope and a lot of hard work,
things will somehow
work out for the best.
I'm not sure I believe that anymore.
You have to, Mel. That's everything.
All I know is
we have a family to look out for.
What if something were to happen
to one of us
or, God forbid, to Gus or Jenny?
Please, don't say that.
How can I not?
It's what I'm thinking.
Isn't it what you're thinking?
Look, it was just one incident,
one crazy person.
Yeah, I...I dearly wish
that I could believe that,
that this kind of thing
will never happen again.
But my grandfather knew
that wasn't true.
That's why he left and came here.
And I know it too.
Are you saying you want to leave?
I don't know what I'm saying.
Oh, God.
I probably sound like
a paranoid, an alarmist.
You're just afraid.
And with good reason.
You know...
..I used to hate it
when Brian would say,
"There are two kinds
of straight people in this world -
"those who hate you to your face
"and those who hate you
behind your back."
Because I knew that wasn't true.
There are plenty of straight people
who don't hate us.
But the ones who do no longer
have to do it behind our backs.
The can do it in the White House,
in...churches,
on television, in the streets.
Is that the kind of place
we want to live?
we want to raise our kids?
Is that the kind of place
Mmm. It's healing very well.
That's good news.
Considering the shape you were in
when they brought you here,
I'd say you're a lucky man.
Whee-hoo!
Um...some interested parties would
like to know when I can go home.
We'll keep you a couple more days,
then send you on your way.
I'm sure they'll be glad
to hear that.
I expect you to take it easy.
Don't overdo.
I heard every word!
I know. Years of practice
listening in on my bedroom door.
I'm glad my superhero's coming home.
Me too.
But you heard the doctor.
You have to rest.
I'll take care of him.
Does this mean no more gang bangs
with the dwarves?
What was that?
I...I was wondering - that is,
if it's alright with you -
if...maybe...I could come home?
Uh...
..I...I think
that would be fine with us.
That's good, because with you
punching people out
and you getting blown up,
somebody really needs
to keep an eye on you.
Anybody home?
Whoa!
Hey, Teddy.
Hey.
Hey, how's it going?
Going good. And where the hell
have you been?
It doesn't matter.
We're just so glad to see you.
You have no idea
how glad I am to see you.
Oh.
So? What's new in the world?
Oh. Uh...let's see. Uh...
Well, uh... Oh, Cher celebrated
her 75th birthday.
And, uh...what else?
Oh, they're doing a new production
of 'Streetcar' down in New York.
Natasha Richardson,
she's going to play Blanche,
and Liz Smith
is going to play Stanley.
When you said there was something
you had to show me,
I didn't think
it would be in West Virginia.
It's less than half an hour
out of Pittsburgh.
Wow.
Wait till you see the tennis court.
And the pool.
And the stables.
Stables? Who lives here?
We do.
What?
I bought it.
You bought this house?
You said that
your small but charmless studio
would have to do
until your country manor came along.
I'd hoped this would be
all you dreamed of.
And more.
But I told you I...
You won't marry me.
Who could blame you?
I am, without doubt, the worst
candidate for marriage alive.
But, conversely, that's also the
reason that I'm the best candidate.
And how's that?
Because, as strongly as I was opposed
to the idea...
..now that I'm behind it,
I am as fervently
and passionately committed.
Uh-huh. And what changed your mind?
I finally thought
of one good reason to do it.
And what is that one good reason?
To prove to the person that I love
how much I love him.
That I would give him anything,
I would...do anything,
I'd be anything...to make him happy.
You're fucking unbelievable. I...
It's true. I am.
You...you bought this?
You bought this palace?!
It's for my prince.
Oh!
I'm also selling the loft
and the club.
Without even knowing
what my answer would be?
I'm taking a chance on love.
Then you mean it.
I've never meant anything more.
ok.
ok?
Let's do it.
Say it.
Yes.
Yes, what?
Yes!
Yes...I will marry you.
I will marry you.
What?
Don't tell me you're already
having second thoughts.
Not one.